Onii-chan!
It's morning!
Wake up!
You're going to be late!
Got it.
Come down soon, okay?
I slept well.
It wasn't a dream?
Onee, breakfast's ready.
Sorry, Iori.
I overslept again.
That's fine, that's fine!
You worked all night. Just relax.
At least drink this before you go.
Oh, I forgot the sugar.
Thanks.
This is all I need.
Did you burn yourself?
No, I'm fine.
Okay.
Who's that, Yoshifumi? A friend?
No one!
Don't read my texts!
Heading out, Himeko?
What, are you blind?
You should lighten up.
You'll never get a boyfriend like that.
Wow, scary.
Morning, Taichi.
Still sleepy?
How are you so full of energy every morning?
Unlike you, I don't watch wrestling all night.
Morning, Inaban!
What, you two come to school together?
No, no. We ran into each other over there.
Oh? Yui! Aoki! Morning!
Morning.
It's almost October, but it's still so hot!
Personally, I think this is just right.
You just can't tell when the season changes.
Right?
Huh? S-Sure.
Here at Yamaboshi High School,
all students are required to join a club and participate in its activities.
But while most wolves hunt in packs, no matter where you go, there will always be lone wolves.
For example, me, who loves wrestling more than anything
and wrote the name of a nonexistent club, the Professional Wrestling Research Society, on my form.
Or, for example,
Kiriyama Yui, who loves cute things and hoped to join the long-defunct Fancy Club.
Aoki Yoshifumi, who sincerely believed that
a club that "hit the town" every night existed and tried to join it.
Or, for example,
Nagase Iori, who thought that, with so many clubs, choosing one would be a hassle
and that leaving the selection to the breeze might give her a fresh and exciting experience,
so she left her club selection
to her homeroom teacher.
Or, for example,
Inaba Himeko, who intended to join the Computing Club, but soon had a falling out with its president,
and ended up having to search for another club.
Oh?
You're the only one here?
As you can see.
And so, these five first-years with nowhere else to go
were lumped together into the newly formed Cultural Research Club,
or CRC for short.
Got an idea for your next article in the CRC News, Taichi?
Of course!
The title is "A History of Professional Wrestling Through Variants of the Brainbuster."
These days, it's common for a brainbuster to involve slamming from the back,
but originally, it was a move where you slammed them from the head—
Shut up.
But you asked.
I only asked if you had an idea.
I made no reference to the content of your article,
nor do I want to hear about it.
As blunt as ever.
Hey! I'm late!
Just Taichi and Inaban?
Yeah. Kiriyama and Aoki aren't here yet.
Darn. I sprinted up the stairs for just you two?
Iori.
Not like it matters.
I'm here too.
120 yen per peek.
You're charging for it?
Though, the price is pretty fair.
What's your next article, Nagase?
I've been thinking about what the CRC News really needs,
and I've concluded that we have a serious lack of erotic and dangerous material.
No one's looking for that sort of excitement from our newspaper.
But I think we need something like that every so often!
So, Inaban, why don't we go for something erotic this time?
Don't make a pure, first-year maiden write an erotic article.
I'm going to write the article.
You just need to let me take a few erotic pictures of you.
Like hell I will!
Besides, you fit the pretty type better than I do.
That kind of stuff suits you more.
No, no. I'm the idol type that you don't shoot nude.
For something more voluptuous, Inaban makes a much better subject.
Voluptuous? I doubt a high school boy would need anything like that.
No, don't you think some "adult charm" is exactly what they're looking for?
Then let's ask a high school boy.
M-Me?
Right, right.
Which one of us would you rather see strip, Taichi?
Wh-Which one?
Well, if I were to represent all high school boys, then I'd say,
"Both of you strip!"
3:55 p.m. Yaegashi Taichi commands two female club members to strip.
Inaban, did you get that?
Of course. This is going in the editorial postscript.
I-I can't deny it because I did say it,
but could you at least make the name anonymous?
No, please make it anonymous.
Um...
What's the matter?
Well, we thought we should tell you about this, but...
...now that we're here, it's kind of...
It kind of takes a bit of courage to say...
Just spit it out!
Okay!
Actually, last night, we...
We switched souls!
Huh?
I'm telling you that Yui and I switched souls!
Like something out of a comic!
Wow! Nice tomahawk chop!
The punchline wasn't as good as the lead-in.
It wasn't a joke! I'm being completely serious here!
I'm more surprised that a bad punchline means a chop from Inaba.
Maybe Yui's rejected you so much that you're deluding yourself?
That would make sense.
How many times have you confessed to her, only to be ignored?
That's not the problem here!
It happened to Yui too!
Right?
When I woke up last night,
I looked around and realized I was in a room I'd never seen before.
And in the mirror, I saw Yui's face and panicked.
But before I knew it, I was back to normal.
The same thing happened to me.
I thought it was a bad dream and buried myself under the covers.
But before I knew it, I was back to normal.
That couldn't possibly have happened.
It couldn't! It definitely couldn't!
Aoki! Don't drag me into your weird delusions!
You're turning your back on me?!
That had to be a bad dream!
So you're saying that we had the same kind of dream
where we switched bodies at the same time,
and that all the stuff I moved in the room when I panicked had moved in reality too?
It's just a bunch of coincidences happening all at once!
Do you get what they're saying?
For the most part.
In other words, a miracle!
And why is it me and you of all people?!
Well, I'm guessing it's fate or destiny or something.
So why don't we just start dating right now?
What led you to that conclusion?
You keep saying creepy stuff like that! That's why!
Iori! This pervert wants me to do weird things!
There, there. It's okay.
You don't have to go that far.
I don't understand any of this!
Will you two just quit it?!
But I can't...
We don't understand any of this either.
I forgot my notebook in the classroom!
Don't change the topic!
Relax, relax!
So, mind if I go get it?
You're the club president.
Don't ask me for permission.
Okay. We can talk more about this later.
Iori's the one person you can't handle.
Guess this is Iori-chan's way of being considerate.
Or is it just coincidence?
It's hard to tell because she may have planned this.
Why don't we have some tea for now?
I'll make some for Nagase too.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Wasn't I...
My voice?!
No way...
Are these...
A-Are these...
Are they... those?
It's my first time touching them, but...
a girl's... a woman's...
things that start with a 'b'?
Nagase-san, what are you doing?
"Nagase-san"?
Nagase?
Nagase-san, what are you doing?
U-Um...
Should I do it for you?
Don't you think it's better if someone else does it for you?
In many ways.
N-No, I'm good, thanks.
Don't be shy now.
I'm very good with my hands.
L-Let's take a step back, Fujishima.
We'll come to an understanding if we just talk things through.
Yes, let's talk...
with our bodies!
O-Our bodies?!
Taichi!
Me?
Yaegashi-kun?
Fujishima-san, if you needed Taichi—I mean, me—I mean, Nagase Iori, then I'm sorry.
This is urgent, so I'm taking her with me.
We're busy right now!
It did look like things were going to get very busy, but...
Let go of me, Fujishima!
See? Taichi—I mean, Nagase wants to go too.
There's something weird about the way you two are talking right now.
Either way, if you're taking Nagase-san, at least tell me why you're taking her.
That doesn't matter! Let go!
If you don't...
No! Stop!
W-Wait, Nagase! You are Nagase, right?
You're me right now, so don't do anything weird!
And that's good enough! Let's go!
That was scary!
I was looking for my notebook, then suddenly I was in the club room.
Everyone called me Taichi.
I freaked out and ran to the classroom.
Aoki and Kiriyama were telling the truth.
What kind of joke is this supposed to be?
Looks like we switched bodies.
Me and Taichi.
I've never seen Taichi smile without a care in the world like this.
There's usually something else behind it.
Yeah.
He's got a good face, too.
Girls would be all over him if he always smiled like this.
Is the way I smile that bad?
You think I care about that?!
You totally hurt your hand just now.
Shut up!
Practicing a dance, Inaban?
I got this one.
She heard Taichi voicing another one of his unnecessary observations
and was going to punish him physically for it as usual,
but then she realized, "Wait, it's actually Iori-chan!" and stopped herself.
An idiot like Aoki talking down to you?
I feel sorry for you, Inaba.
But I've never seen Inaba so happy before.
I'll get you back for that one, Tai—
Inaban, you were just about to call Nagase Iori "Taichi."
B-Because...
you two keep putting on this stupid act!
You think Taichi could pretend to be me this well?
Inaba, you might not believe it, but please try.
I'm Yaegashi Taichi.
Yui, Aoki, what do you think?
There's no doubt in my mind that Taichi and Iori-chan switched bodies.
Wouldn't you agree, Yui?
I guess I have to accept it.
Oh?
Sounds like you'll have to accept our switch too.
I will.
I mean, with Iori and Taichi like this...
But don't you all think you're accepting it way too easily?
Well, if it happened to you, all you could say is "Oh, that's what happened!"
This is giving me a headache.
I'll ask you one more time.
You're saying that you're not just trying to screw with me
and that Iori's and Taichi's personalities really got switched?
That means that you know things only Taichi would know.
Yeah. Ask me anything you want.
You have less than one second.
All right.
What's the title of the last adult film that Taichi borrowed from Aoki?
High School Girls with Huge Boobs—
What kind of question is that?!
You don't even know the answer to it!
That doesn't matter.
Aoki's here to check your answer.
So Taichi, what's the answer?
Um...
Huge boobs, huh?
Excuse me, Inaba-san,
would you mind if I whispered it into Aoki's ear?
Was that the title, Aoki?
It certainly was, Captain Inaba!
And hearing dirty words from Iori-chan's mouth turned me on a bit!
Wait, why does it feel like I lost something important?
Now that we know that the guys are both boob men,
let's see if this one is really Iori.
I-Is it just me, or is Inaba simultaneously determining if we're telling the truth
and getting revenge on us for making fun of her?
I hope I never get on Inaba's bad side...
Wait! Inaban, are you serious?!
I am.
But I guess that's how we grow up...
What did Inaba-chan just tell her?
So you switched personalities.
I'll accept it.
If we compare the probability of Taichi being able to show this much emotion, even if he were acting,
and the probability of people switching personalities,
the latter is far greater.
I don't know how to respond to that opinion.
So, what are you going to do now?
I wonder.
Aoki, Kiriyama, how long were you switched for?
30 or 40 minutes, I guess.
Do you think it's for a set amount of time?
Or maybe...
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
We're back to normal!
You can't be serious...
I still can't believe that really happened.
Well, maybe we could just say that it's been a strange day?
I don't know.
Was it just a one-day phenomenon?
Was it just something that happened to you four?
In any case, let's not tell anyone about it for now.
I wouldn't want my family to worry about me.
Yeah, and I doubt that anyone would believe us if we did.
Was it really only a one-day thing?
Oh?
Welcome back.
Thanks.
Oh, Himeko, you're home?
Seriously, are you blind?
What's up? You seem angrier than usual.
Nothing. This is how I always am.
Onee, are you okay?
You didn't look so good this morning.
Oh, I'm fine.
I just didn't get enough sleep.
Don't worry about it.
Hello?
Mom?
You're working late again today?
It's okay! I already ate.
Don't overwork yourself now.
Bye.
Onii-chan!
Hey. Heading home now?
Yeah.
I had a meeting that ran really late.
I'm so tired.
Sounds like a rough day.
How about some ice cream?
Onii-chan, stop treating me like such a kid!
I'm in fifth grade now!
So you don't want any?
I do.
Did you three switch bodies this time, or something?
Why is your name the same as some obscure plant's?
Once it happens, it's too late!
I'm...
not him, after all.